(Penny:)-You're extorting a date out of me?
-I kind of have to.
(Stuart:)The cousin who's getting married is
the cousin I usually go to weddings with.
(Penny:)-Can I bring Leonard?
-Sure. What the hell?
(Leonard:)-Deal.
-We'll tell people he's your cousin.
(Sheldon:)This is Stan Lee's front door.
(Sheldon:)We were on Stan Lee's curb,
then we were on Stan Lee's walk...
(Sheldon:)-...and now we're at Stan Lee's front door.
-Yep.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord, you just rang Stan Lee's
doorbell at Stan Lee's house.
(Sheldon:)We're about to go in and
have milk and cookies with Stan Lee.
(Penny:)Sweetie, I don't know if we're gonna
have cookies or what's gonna happen...
(Penny:)...so just let me talk and--
(Penny:)Yeah?
(Penny:)-Are you Stan Lee?
-Oh, damn.
(Penny:)Hi. I'm Penny.
This is my friend Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)We're not friends at the moment.
Depends on how this goes.
(Penny:)Right, right. Anyway,
Sheldon here is a huge fan of yours.